So I'm kind of like disassociating because I just don't like have the capacity today.
So I figured I'd show you guys some of my art because maybe you didn't know that I do visual art.
So I figured I would show you guys some of my visual art.
So I guess I should take them out of this thing.
So this is a piece that I did called Guardian Angel.
It's on like a 24 by 36 campus.
And Debbie Dev actually bought this piece.
So shout out to Debbie Dev.
And I did this piece after a breakup because I felt like I am always like armored up, but still have vulnerabilities.
So it makes it to where you you're like guarded, but you're not fully protected.
And so Debbie Dev owns that piece.
And then I wasn't done.
I wasn't done.
So I did a part two and this one I still own.
So this one is, um, y'all, this fig tree is fake.
This fig tree, this is a fake tree.
This tree is fake.
So clearly I got the right tree because y'all think it's real.
And so I'm, I'm like, good job seals.
So I've been, um, tidying up an area of my crib that I hadn't really been like paying attention to.
So I came across stuff.
So this is one of my favorite pieces called From the Womb to the Boom.
And it is, um, about all the hip hop heads.
So as you can see, she's sitting on turntables and the headphones are plugged directly into the womb.
Um, and the skyline depicts like cities all over that are, you know, kind of hip hop.
Man, what y'all break now?
Um, and then down here represents the, the elements of hip hop.
You got the kicks for the B-boys.
There's a purple tape for, uh, only built for Cuban links.
There's, there's a spray can and a marker for the graffiti guy, for the graph artists.
And there's, uh, the turntables and the records for DJs.
And the mic around her neck is to represent the MCs.
So I mean, I love a theme.
I love a theme.
Part two.
So this is part two from the womb to the boom part two.
And, um, you know, similar elements just represented differently.
And, um, these were painted, phew, man.
Oh, like, oh, oh, well, I would have graduated school.
So these, these are painted like, oh, four, oh, five.
And, um, uh, I paint in acrylic.
I need to learn oil, but it just hasn't, I haven't gotten there yet.
And, um, this image here on the train is a shout out to my favorite graffiti artist,
Dondi.
Rest in peace.
Um, and, uh, what does NTG mean?
What does NTG mean?
Oh, you're just putting letters up on screen.
Okay.
Um, did I use canvas paper and printed a copy?
Or did you do framed canvas?
Framed canvas.
A stretched canvas.
Not canvas paper.
Is that what?
No, that's what I thought NTG meant.
And not that good.
But then I was like, Amanda, you're, you're being self-deprecating because you're, you're
being vulnerable by showing your art.
I don't know if y'all know who DJ Self is.
Shout out to DJ Self.
DJ Self was a really, he, I mean, he's the homie for life.
But when I was younger, he was, uh, and I was working at Sirius Satellite Radio.
I don't sell these anywhere right now.
Um, I, I need to put them up on my site, but I got to figure out a printer that's at a level that I would like.
Like, I, I agree with you, a frastic post, poet.
Um, but this is a painting of a DJ.
I had originally painted this for DJ Self and then I kept it.
Um, but they're rocking, oh, NTG need to go.
Okay.
Um, so this is DJ Self rocking, um, like the, the, the party of the lifetime.
Like, like, like Billy Joel has a song, um, called Miami.
I think it's like Miami 2020 or something like that.
And it's like, I seen the lights go out on Broadway.
Watch the Empire state land low.
Anyways, it just like, it's like a song about like culmination.
And that's what this feels like.
Um, and you know, like there's elements, like this is like a tape deck.
This is a crate, you know, it's like a crate, um, shelf.
And I actually put like little slivers of my favorite albums in here.
I need to go look at the original.
And like this, see, this is like a mixer.
It has faders and dials.
Oh yeah, I'm good.
I'm good for Debo in my own paintings.
No, I don't smoke.
My brain is just on one.
So I also like masks is like a very common theme of mine.
Um, and hey, Miss Debbie, masks is a very common, common theme of mine.
Um, so this is on a 34 by, no, 28 by 36 canvas.
And, um, the, the theme with the masks is symmetry.
But a lot of times it's like, I'll like do a painting for someone and then they'll piss
me off.
And so then they don't get the painting no more.
Like I had originally painted this for Lupe, but then he pissed me off.
So I kept the painting.
Um, so, you know, if, if, if you want a painting from me, don't fucking piss me, don't piss me
off.
So then I also have these Afro series.
These are like a big theme.
And, um, this was the first one I ever did of the, of this style.
And I did this live.
I did this live at a live painting event and, you know, it really worked out as like a useful
lifestyle because I can paint the, um, the designs like really fast.
So what I do is I paint the background first and then I go over and I freehand the black
lines.
And then I go in and I highlight with the white and, you know, it's, it's pretty low
impact in terms of like what I'm putting out, but I'm able to get like a very high yield
out of that.
Here's another, here's another one.
And both of these paintings ended up selling.
So I actually don't have these anymore.
When I was moving from New York in 2015, people, um, bought them.
So I was really lucky.
I was really, and I, I, and I needed, I needed that.
Um, hold on.
And then there's this one.
So this one, you got to get like real close.
People always say she looks like Beyonce.
And then, um, I like to do, I like to draw with pen a lot.
So I do a lot of pen and ink, not someone saying, Oh, you are autistic.
Yes.
So, you know, it's funny how that person just said, Oh, you are autistic.
Because these drawings I did when I was in class and I would literally tell the professor,
like, I'm gonna, my head is going to be down, but it doesn't mean I'm not listening to you.
I'm drawing so that I can listen.
And, um, I didn't even realize that that was a part of autism, but it really, but it is.
And so like, that's like a key element.
Like sometimes y'all see me on panels and I might be looking down drawing.
I might be looking down drawing and it like, looks like I'm not participating,
but I'm not going to mask for anyone anymore.
So it's like, no, I'm participating.
This is how I participate.
I draw.
So, um, you know, these are some of my drawings and, um, I'm gonna, I'm, I'm hoping to do more
drawing and stuff and figuring out how to make them available to you guys and whatnot.
But I, I hope that, um, you're taking care of yourselves and drawing is something that
helps me take care of myself, helps me get out of rumination cycles and, you know, painting
is something that also is a good regulator.
So I really need to like, get back to that.
And, um, this was a shirt I just, I painted.
So anywho, I had just found this, this, um, portfolio that I had put together of my art.
I'm not even sure why I had made this portfolio.
I don't know what job I was trying to get or what, but I had a portfolio of some of my art
and I was like, let me show the people.
So shout out to all the artists out there who are, you know, putting their pain and their
joy and all the things into their craft.
And, um, you know, I, I, I also, someone in here said they, they wish they, they think
that art will save the world and I don't disagree.
I don't disagree.
So y'all have a great one.
Did I do the artwork for small doses podcast cover?
I sure did.
I've done the artwork for all my logos.
So I'm actually going to put a small doses shirt up for sales shortly.
And it'll have on the back, it'll have all the episodes, all 400 episodes that we did
of small doses.
I cannot believe I did 400 episodes of small doses podcast.
Anywho, just thought I would share with y'all real quick.
And, um, sending love your way, sending strength and sending regulation, but you can go actually
to amandalandexports.com and check out what I do have up there.